Let me greet you once again.
Good morning. We are Bolt. Nice to meet you.
Please take care of the day's shooting.
I heard a rumor that my bicycle is the heaviest.
I'm thinking, "Oh no, what if I don't get burnt?
I'll do my best.
Ready?
It's okay, it's okay.
How far do you want me to go?
See you next time,
Talinko, are you okay?
I was fine.
It's pretty thrilling.
It's going to be like this back here.
This one, this one,
This... this... this...
It's going to be like this all the way down.
Hang in there.
Next, let's go up this hill,
I'm going to challenge you and push,
I'll get up.
Yes, let's go.
Dash, dash. Run up pretty fast.
Cut!
Is it hard?
Well, I'm a little nervous about the way I'm running again.
When I'm being filmed from behind.
I have a bicycle, so it can't be helped.
It's the bicycle's fault.
I feel like I'm running pretty.
I have this image in my head, but what do you think?
Wait a minute.
Don't worry, I'm being nice.
I'm feeling a little more confident.
Wow, I can ride. Look at all the people.
Yay! Like this.
Yay!
This is also a 54 year old jiggly jiggly drain for anyone who is interested in me.
will be the next playback daemon!
Hello.
I just got off track.
Twenty years go
It's been a long time since I've ridden a train, and I'm enjoying it.
I feel like it's a little late for this
Oh, wow!
huh?
I'm here to use it.
I've come to use it a lot, haven't I?
I'm sorry.
But it kind of reminds me of the first time I rode a bike.
Surprisingly, I can go pretty far.
I'm sure it's the tires.
I don't know.
I don't know, but they seem a little sturdy.
They're kind of stiff.
Good night.
I want everyone to go where Aya-chan is going now.
Yes.
You can see.
On your marks.
All right, Don!
Cut!
The world is in trouble.
Good morning.
I am sure you will eat a lot of food today,
I'm sure you will eat a lot of dinner at home,
It's all right.
Where are you coming from?
Where did you come from?
Where they come from, where they come from,
I'm just trying to move around a little bit.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know where they went.
I'm going to get a lot of exercise.
I'm going to exercise a lot.
I'm going to eat a lot.
And eat a lot.
Before I knew it, I was chasing after him.
Ah, I was walking alone.
Don't say goodbye.
I wanted to say goodbye.
Yeah, but not yet.
Yeah, but still.
You're giving me warmth.
Don't say goodbye.
I'll try my best at dancing.
Please do.
This costume is over.
Oh, I see.
See you later.
Bye bye.
I'm going to change.
See you.
I want to run a story that's just the two of us... because I know, in my own literal way, that it's a precious memory, and it's shining.
But I can't really tell where they are right now.
It would be nice if it was a little cooler.
Sorry.
It would be nice.
Aya!
Nanny.
I knew it!
Yeah.
Nana-chan
Aya-chan
Aya.
Yes.
I knew it!
There is this kind of swing, but you have to swing like this. I tend to swing like this.
So, do your best. Sideways swinging.
I do that too.
I get scared when I dance.
You know those people playing the tambourine? One-handed tambourine.
Yes, cut!
That's all for today. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
We have just finished shooting the music video for Accent.
It's been a while since we ended the shoot with a dance scene.
It feels fresh.
We had costumes made for the music video, and I think it has a story-like feel to it, like the popularity of labor,
It's a little bit like how the members met and did what they did.
Indeed, indeed.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been waiting for the members while licking Chupa Chups.
How many Chupa Chups have you had, Aya? This is the third one today.
That's right.
I took all the photos today before the sunset, so the sun was really beautiful,
I was able to be involved in nature a lot during the sunrise and sunset.
We were blessed, weren't we?
It was great.
I liked the way Ahmadjon dressed me.
All of the bicycles were stylish, and each bicycle had a different color.
Maybe because the bicycles were stylish, the way they were ridden also looked stylish.
I was with Chii-chan when she first started riding,
I was looking at them.
Did you see it?
Oh no! I have no idea.
It's not the scene where she's trying hard to ride a bike.
That's for sure.
It's like a documentary.It's like a documentary.
I'm sure it's just a good part of it.
I think that's probably true, so please watch this music video as much as you can.
That's all for us, Bolt.
Bye bye!